freewareppc.com 2011-12-04

# FreewarePPC.com - Freeware Pocket PC / Freeware Windows Mobile: Privacy Statement

FreewarePPC.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our Website. In order to enhance your experience at our site we gather certain personal information about you that helps us customize our content to your tastes and preferences.  
Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Web site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

FreewarePPC.com collects and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site, and to help identify you. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and for other purposes. 

FreewarePPC.com collects some personal information when you initially access our site. We may ask for your name, e-mail address, zip code, and country. The more information you share with us (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to enhance and customize your experience on our site. 

FreewarePPC.com run submission form in which we ask the visitors for their email address. This email address we obtain from visitors will not be sold or shared with any third party. All information gathered is used for internal purposes only.   
All files content and ownership remain to the creator of that files. We are not in any way responsible for checking out the content or functionally of them, but are merely listing them for your convenience. Please direct any comments, questions and feedback to the author's e-mail link. 

FreewarePPC.com use some outside ad companies to display ads on the site. These ads may contain cookies. While we do not use cookies in our website, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. 

FreewarePPC.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users. Staff overlook server access daily to ensure the above holds true. 

FreewarePPC.com site contains links to other sites and file downloads from other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

FreewarePPC.com works with some third party that serves ads to the site. To find out more about how they manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to their sites: [Google](https://www.google.com/adsense/policies?hl=en_US), [ValueClick](http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml). 

FreewarePPC.com also partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit <http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>.

By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by FreewarePPC.com as outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [privacy@freewareppc.com](mailto:privacy@freewareppc.com).   
For other questions regarding the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, contact [webmaster@freewareppc.com](mailto:webmaster@freewareppc.com).
